Sound Recordings of Museum-Related Events
The Museum of Modern Art, Publisher
- General Sound Recordings of Museum-Related Activities, 1939-present
  - "Beaumont Newhall Memorial Tribute", October 6, 1993; PLACE: The Museum of Modern Art PARTICIPANTS: Richard Oldenburg, Director, The Museum of Modern Art; James Enyeart, author; Sarah Greenough, Curator of Photography Department, National Gallery of Art, DC; Van Deren Coke, photographer; John Szarkowski, photographer. SUMMARY: A discussion of Beaumont Newhall's legacy and love of photography. DATA: Two standard 90 minute audio cassette tapes. TRANSFERRED TO ARCHIVES: October 2006 (Item 2006.40a)
  - "Beaumont Newhall Memorial Tribute", October 6, 1993; PLACE: The Museum of Modern Art PARTICIPANTS: Richard Oldenburg, Director, The Museum of Modern Art; James Enyeart, author; Sarah Greenough,Curator of Photography Department, National Gallery of Art, DC; Van Deren Coke, photographer; John Szarkowski, photographer. SUMMARY: A discussion of Beaumont Newhall's legacy and love of photography. DATA: Two standard 90 minute audio cassette tapes. TRANSFERRED TO ARCHIVES: October 2006 (Item 2006.40b)
  - "Opening of Joan Mir Exhibition", October 13, 1993; PARTICIPANTS: Richard Oldenburg, Director, The Museum of Modern Art; Agnes Gund, President, The Museum of Modern Art; Fracisco Luzan, Chairman of Argemtaria; Juan Carlos, King of Spain. SPONSOR: Argemtaria EXHIBITION:Joan Mir[MoMA Exh. #166, October 13, 1993-January 11, 1994] SUMMARY: A discussion of past Mir exhibitions, and the philosophy behind the current Mir exhibition. Also includes a lengthy acknowledgment of lenders and the King and Queen of Spain. DATA: One standard 90 minute audio cassette tape; Duplicate is 1 90 Minute Standard Audio Cassette. DONOR: Department of Special Events TRANSFERRED TO ARCHIVES: October 2006; Duplicate arrived July 2004 (Item 2006.41, 2006.41D)
  - "The Aroma of Enchantment", December 11, 1992; NOTE: This recording does not include the beginning of the premiere.; PERSONALITY: Chip Lord PLACE: Titus Theater 2, The Museum of Modern Art SERIES: Video Premieres PARTICIPANTS: Chip Lord, media artist. SUMMARY: The premier of Chip Lord's film "The Aroma of Enchantment," a film that investigates the idea of the "American Dream" in Japan. DATA: One standard 90 minute audio cassette tape. DONOR: Department of Film and Video TRANSFERRED TO ARCHIVES: October 2006 (Item 2006.42)
  - "Video Program: Interviews by Barbara London with Bill Viola", May 17, 1986; PERSONALITY: Bill Viola PLACE: Titus Theater 2, The Museum of Modern Art SERIES: "Interviews by Barbara London" PARTICIPANTS: Barbara London, assistant curator, Department of Film and Video, The Museum of Modern Art; Bill Viola, artist. SUMMARY: Barbara London and Bill Viola discuss his creative process and inspiration. DATA: One standard 90 minute audio cassette tape. DONOR: Department of Film and Video TRANSFERRED TO ARCHIVES: October 2006 (Item 2006.43)
  - "Video Program: Interviews by Barbara London with Laurie Anderson", February 1985; PERSONALITY: Laurie Anderson PLACE: Titus Theater 2, The Museum of Modern Art SERIES: Interviews by Barbara London PARTICIPANTS: Barbara London, assistant curator, Department of Film and Video, The Museum of Modern Art; Laurie Anderson, experimental performer and musician. SUMMARY: Music from Laurie Anderson as well as interview about her uses of new media. DATA: One standard 90 minute audio cassette tape. DONOR: Department of Film and Video TRANSFERRED TO ARCHIVES: October 2006 (Item 2006.44)
  - "Sound Art", June 25-August 5, 1979; PERSONALITY: Julia Heyward and D. Christensen PLACE: The Museum of Modern Art SERIES: Interviews by Barbara London PARTICIPANTS: Barbara London, assistant curator, Department of Film and Video, The Museum of Modern Art; Julia Heyward, artist; D. Christensen, artist. EXHIBITION:Sound Art[MoMA Exh. #1266, June 25-July 5, 1979] SUMMARY: Soundtrack to their installation, including "Nova Convention", "It's Raining Blood", "Bury me in 2001", "Apocalupso." DATA: One standard 90 minute audio cassette tape. DONOR: Department of Film and Video TRANSFERRED TO ARCHIVES: October 2006 (Item 2006.45)
  - "Video Program: Interviews by Barbara London: Michael Shamberg", November 17 - January 10, 1989; NOTE: This recording is damaged and does not play in its entirety.; PERSONALITY: Michael Shamberg PLACE: The Museum of Modern Art SERIES: Interviews by Barbara London PARTICIPANTS: Barbara London, assistant curator, Department of Film and Video, The Museum of Modern Art; Deirdre Boyle, historian; Michael Shamberg, video artist. EXHIBITION:American Documentary Video[MoMA Exh. #1505, November 17, 1988-January 10, 1989] SUMMARY: An interview of Michael Shamberg, an original member of TVTV collective, performed by Barbara London and Deirdre Boyle on the occasion of the show "American Documentary Video: Subject to Change." DATA: One standard 90 minute audio cassette tape. DONOR: Department of Film and Video TRANSFERRED TO ARCHIVES: October 2006 (Item 2006.46)
  - "Henri Matisse and Costume", April 8, 1996; PERSONALITY: Francis Mason PLACE: WQXR Radio Station PARTICIPANTS: Francis Mason, radio announcer for WQRX, the radio station for the New York Times. EXHIBITION:Henri Matisse: A Retrospective[MoMA Exh. #1633, September 24, 1992-January 1993, 1993] SUMMARY: Francis Mason discusses costume and dance within the Matisse exhibition. DATA: One 60 Minute Standard Audio Cassette tape. TRANSFERRED TO ARCHIVES: October 2006 (Item 2006.47)
  - "Zero Degrees Latitude", October 8, 1993; PERSONALITY: Steve Fagin PLACE: Titus Theater 2, The Museum of Modern Art SERIES: Video Premieres PARTICIPANTS: Barbara London, assistant curator, Department of Film and Video, The Museum of Modern Art; Steve Fagin, Cinematographer. SUMMARY: Steve Fagin premieres his film "Zero Degrees Latitude" and discusses the making of the film. DATA: One standard 60 minute audio cassette tape. DONOR: Department of Film and Video TRANSFERRED TO ARCHIVES: October 2006 (Item 2006.48)
  - "Judith Barry Interview", March 25, 1986; NOTE: This recording does not start at the beginning of the interview.; PERSONALITY: Judith Barry PLACE: The Museum of Modern Art SERIES: Barbara London Interviews PARTICIPANTS: Barbara London, assistant curator, Department of Film and Video, The Museum of Modern Art; Judith Barry, artist. SUMMARY: Judith Barry speaks about her use of material and her installation methods, specifically her work "Echo." DATA: Two standard 60 minute audio cassette tapes. DONOR: Department of Film and Video TRANSFERRED TO ARCHIVES: October 2006 (Item 2006.49a)
  - "Judith Barry Interview", March 25, 1986; NOTE: This recording does not start at the beginning of the interview.; PERSONALITY: Judith Barry PLACE: The Museum of Modern Art SERIES: Barbara London Interviews PARTICIPANTS: Barbara London, assistant curator, Department of Film and Video, The Museum of Modern Art; Judith Barry, artist. SUMMARY: Judith Barry speaks about her use of material and her installation methods, specifically her work "Echo." DATA: Two standard 60 minute audio cassette tapes. DONOR: Department of Film and Video TRANSFERRED TO ARCHIVES: October 2006 (Item 2006.49b)
  - "S Tanikawa Interview", February 26, 1989; NOTE: The recording begins in the middle of the interview.; PERSONALITY: S Tanikawa PLACE: Titus Theater 2, The Museum of Modern Art SERIES: Barbara London Interviews PARTICIPANTS: Barbara London, assistant curator, Department of Film and Video, The Museum of Modern Art; S Tanikawa, artist. SUMMARY: Discussion between Barbara London and S Tanikawa concerning his collaborative works. DATA: Two standard 60 minute audio cassette tape. DONOR: Department of Film and Video TRANSFERRED TO ARCHIVES: October 2006 (Item 2006.50a)
  - "S Tanikawa Interview", February 26, 1989; NOTE: The recording begins in the middle of the interview.; PERSONALITY: S Tanikawa PLACE: Titus Theater 2, The Museum of Modern Art SERIES: Barbara London Interviews PARTICIPANTS: Barbara London, assistant curator, Department of Film and Video, The Museum of Modern Art; S Tanikawa, artist. SUMMARY: Discussion between Barbara London and S Tanikawa concerning his collaborative works. DATA: Two standard 60 minute audio cassette tape. DONOR: Department of Film and Video TRANSFERRED TO ARCHIVES: October 2006 (Item 2006.50b)
  - "Edin Velez", September 6, 1989; PERSONALITY: Edin Velez PLACE: Titus Theater 2, The Museum of Modern Art SERIES: Interviews by Barbara London PARTICIPANTS: Barbara London, assistant curator, Department of Film and Video, The Museum of Modern Art; Edin Velez, artist. SUMMARY: Edin Velez speaks about his Japanese and Latin influences. DATA: One standard 60 minute audio cassette tape. DONOR: Department of Film and Video TRANSFERRED TO ARCHIVES: October 2006 (Item 2006.51a)
  - "Edin Velez", September 6, 1989; PERSONALITY: Edin Velez PLACE: Titus Theater 2, The Museum of Modern Art SERIES: Interviews by Barbara London PARTICIPANTS: Barbara London, assistant curator, Department of Film and Video, The Museum of Modern Art; Edin Velez, artist. SUMMARY: Edin Velez speaks about his Japanese and Latin influences. DATA: One standard 60 minute audio cassette tape. DONOR: Department of Film and Video TRANSFERRED TO ARCHIVES: October 2006 (Item 2006.51b)
  - "Suburbs of Eden", October 16, 1992; PERSONALITY: Cecilia Condit PLACE: Titus Theater 2, The Museum of Modern Art SERIES: Video Premieres PARTICIPANTS: Barbara London, assistant curator, Department of Film and Video, The Museum of Modern Art; Cecilia Condit, Cinematographer. SUMMARY: Cecilia Condit premieres her film "Suburbs of Eden" and discusses the making of the film. DATA: One standard 60 minute audio cassette tape. DONOR: Department of Film and Video TRANSFERRED TO ARCHIVES: October 2006 (Item 2006.52)
  - "The Note", June 25-August 5, 1979; PERSONALITY: Connie Beckley PLACE: The Museum of Modern Art EXHIBITION:Sound Art[MoMA Exh. #1266, June 25-July 5, 1979] SUMMARY: Connie Beckley's audio performance of "The Note" with musical score. DATA: One standard 60 minute audio cassette tape. DONOR: Department of Film and Video TRANSFERRED TO ARCHIVES: October 2006 (Item 2006.53)
  - "Day Without Art", December 3, 1993; PERSONALITY: Greg Bordowitz SERIES: Video Program PARTICIPANTS: Greg Bordowitz, AIDS activist and Filmmaker. SUMMARY: Greg Bordowitz shows a documentary about the AIDS crisis in the early 90's. DATA: One standard 60 minute audio cassette tape. DONOR: Department of Film and Video TRANSFERRED TO ARCHIVES: October 2006 (Item 2006.54)
  - "Seven Fron Three (for go)", August 6 - September 15, 1981; PERSONALITY: Alan Scarritt PLACE: Titus Theater 2, The Museum of Modern Art SERIES: Projects (Installation) PARTICIPANTS: Alan Scarritt, artist. EXHIBITION:Alan Scarritt[MoMA Exh. #1315, August 6-September 15, 1981] SUMMARY: Audio of the installation "Seven Fron Three (for go)" from the Alan Scarritt exhibition. DATA: One standard 90 minute audio cassette tape. DONOR: Department of Film and Video TRANSFERRED TO ARCHIVES: October 2006 (Item 2006.55, 2006.55D)
  - "Summergarden at The Museum of Modern Art", 1992; PERSONALITY: Lloyd Moss SERIES: Traditions PARTICIPANTS: Lloyd Moss, host. SUMMARY: Lloyd Moss, host of Paine Webber's Concert Network, discusses MoMA's sculpture garden, the summergarden concert series and plays Claude Debussy recording. DATA: One standard 90 minute audio cassette tape; Duplicate is 1 Standard Audio Cassette. DONOR: Department of Film and Video TRANSFERRED TO ARCHIVES: October 2006 (Item 2006.56, 2006.56D)
  - "Projects: Shigeko Kubota", PERSONALITY: Shigeko Kubota PLACE: The Museum of Modern Art SERIES: Projects PARTICIPANTS: Shigeko Kubota, visual artist; Kazuko Oshima, actor. EXHIBITION:Projects: Shigeko Kubota[MoMA Exh. #1203, March 16-May 2, 1978] SUMMARY: Shigeko Kubota discusses her Japanese heritage and her conceptual work. Kazuko Oshima records the lecture. DATA: One standard 90 minute audio cassette tape. DONOR: Department of Film and Video TRANSFERRED TO ARCHIVES: October 2006 (Item 2006.57)
  - "Sound Art", June 25-August 5, 1979; PERSONALITY: Maggie Payne PLACE: The Museum of Modern Art PARTICIPANTS: Maggie Payne, artist. EXHIBITION:Sound Art[MoMA Exh. #1266, June 25-July 5, 1979] SUMMARY: Sound from Maggie Payne's installation "Lunar Dusk" and "Lunar Earthrise." DATA: One standard 60 minute audio cassette tape. DONOR: Department of Film and Video TRANSFERRED TO ARCHIVES: October 2006 (Item 2006.58)
  - "Gordon Bunshaft Memorial Tribute", September 19, 1990; PLACE: The Museum of Modern Art PARTICIPANTS: Richard Oldenburg, Director, The Museum of Modern Art; Charles Bassett, architect; David Rockefeller, chairman of the Board, The Museum of Modern Art; Philip Johnson, architect and curator; William Rubin, curator, Department of Painting and Sculpture, The Museum of Modern Art; Kevin Roche, architect; Leon Moed, architect. SUMMARY: Acknowledgments of Gordon Bunshaft's career and achievements. DATA: One standard 90 minute audio cassette tape. DONOR: Department of Film and Video TRANSFERRED TO ARCHIVES: October 2006 (Item 2006.59)
  - "Matisse Picasso on WNYC", PLACE: WNYC Station, New York NY PARTICIPANTS: John Elderfield, curator, Department of Painting and Sculpture, The Museum of Modern Art; Kirk Varnedoe, Chief Curator, Department of Painting and Sculpture, The Museum of Modern Art. EXHIBITION:Matisse Picasso[MoMA Exh. #1906, February 13-May 19, 2003] DATA: One standard 90 minute audio cassette tape. DONOR: Department of Painting and Sculpture TRANSFERRED TO ARCHIVES: November 2006 (Item 2006.60, 2006.60D)
  - "Master Drawings Symposium", December 9, 2000; PLACE: Titus Theater 2, The Museum of Modern Art. DATA: Eight standard 90 minute audio cassette tape. DONOR: Department of Painting and Sculpture TRANSFERRED TO ARCHIVES: November 2006 (Item 2006.61a, 2006.61aD)
  - "Master Drawings Symposium", December 9, 2000; PLACE: Titus Theater 2, The Museum of Modern Art. DATA: Eight standard 90 minute audio cassette tape. DONOR: Department of Painting and Sculpture TRANSFERRED TO ARCHIVES: November 2006 (Item 2006.61b, 2006.61bD)
  - "Master Drawings Symposium", December 9, 2000; PLACE: Titus Theater 2, The Museum of Modern Art. DATA: Eight standard 90 minute audio cassette tape. DONOR: Department of Painting and Sculpture TRANSFERRED TO ARCHIVES: November 2006 (Item 2006.61c, 2006.61cD)
  - "Master Drawings Symposium", December 9, 2000; PLACE: Titus Theater 2, The Museum of Modern Art. DATA: Eight standard 90 minute audio cassette tape. DONOR: Department of Painting and Sculpture TRANSFERRED TO ARCHIVES: November 2006 (Item 2006.61d, 2006.61dD)
  - "The Vision of the Modern", September 27-29, 1985; PERSONALITY: Richard Oldenburg SERIES: The Tarrytown Group, New Museums New Audiences PARTICIPANTS: Richard Oldenburg, Director, The Museum of Modern Art SUMMARY: Discussion about the history of the museums numerous construction projects and the changes the museum had gone through in the public eye. DATA: 1 60 Minute Standard Audio Cassette RELATED MATERIAL: 96.22, 96.23a, 96.23b, 96.24a, 96.24b. TRANSFERRED TO ARCHIVES: November 2006 (Item 2006.62)
  - "Echo", March 25, 1986; PERSONALITY: Judith Barry SERIES: Video Program PARTICIPANTS: Judith Barry, artist EXHIBITION:Projects: Judith Barry[MoMA Exh. #1421, May 2-June 3, 1986] SUMMARY: Audio component of Echo DATA: 1 60 Minute Audio Cassette RELATED MATERIAL: 2006.49a, 2006.49b. DONOR: Department of Film TRANSFERRED TO ARCHIVES: November 2006 (Item 2006.63)
  - "Pioneering Modern Painting: A Symposium on Czanne and Pissarro", September 10, 2005; PLACE: Titus Theater 1, The Museum of Modern Art PARTICIPANTS: Joachim Pissarro, curator, Department of Painting and Sculpture, The Museum of Modern Art; Tim Clark, Professor at University of California, Berkeley; Paul Smith, art historian; Brett Littman, Deputy Director, P.S.1. EXHIBITION:Pioneering Modern Painting: Czanne and Pissarro 1865-1885[MoMA Exh. #1944, June 26, 2005 September 12, 2005] SUMMARY: The afternoon session of this symposium was centered around anarchism and realism. DATA: 2 90 Minute Standard Audio Cassettes. RELATED MATERIAL: 2006.38a, 2006.38b. DONOR: Department of Painting and Sculpture. TRANSFERRED TO ARCHIVES: November 2006 (Item 2006.64a)
  - "Pioneering Modern Painting: A Symposium on Czanne and Pissarro", September 10, 2005; PLACE: Titus Theater 1, The Museum of Modern Art PARTICIPANTS: Joachim Pissarro, curator, Department of Painting and Sculpture, The Museum of Modern Art; Tim Clark, Professor at University of California, Berkeley; Paul Smith, art historian; Brett Littman, Deputy Director, P.S.1. EXHIBITION:Pioneering Modern Painting: Czanne and Pissarro 1865-1885[MoMA Exh. #1944, June 26, 2005 September 12, 2005] SUMMARY: The afternoon session of this symposium was centered around anarchism and realism. DATA: 2 90 Minute Standard Audio Cassettes. RELATED MATERIAL: 2006.38a, 2006.38b. DONOR: Department of Painting and Sculpture. TRANSFERRED TO ARCHIVES: November 2006 (Item 2006.64b)
  - "Elizabeth Murray: A Critics Panel", November 28, 2005; PERSONALITY: Elizabeth Murray PLACE: Titus Theater 2, The Museum of Modern Art SERIES: Adult and Academic Programs PARTICIPANTS: Robert Storr, Chief Curator, Department of Painting and Sculpture, The Museum of Modern Art; Carter Ratcliff, editor,Art in America; Katy Siegel, art historian and critic; Joan Simon, contributing editor to Art in America; Alexi Worth, artist. EXHIBITION:Elizabeth Murray[MoMA Exh. #1955, October 28, 2005 - January 9, 2006] DATA: 1 of 2 Standard CDs SUMMARY: Participants give presentations and engage in discussions moderated by Robert Storr. RELATED MATERIAL: 2006.36 DONOR: Department of Education TRANSFERRED TO ARCHIVES: Fall 2006; NOTE: This recording is extremely difficult to hear (Item 2006.65a)
  - "Elizabeth Murray: A Critics Panel", November 28, 2005; PERSONALITY: Elizabeth Murray PLACE: Titus Theater 2, The Museum of Modern Art SERIES: Adult and Academic Programs PARTICIPANTS: Robert Storr, Chief Curator, Department of Painting and Sculpture, The Museum of Modern Art; Carter Ratcliff, editor, Art in America; Katy Siegel, art historian and critic; Joan Simon, contributing editor to Art in America; Alexi Worth, artist. EXHIBITION:Elizabeth Murray[MoMA Exh. #1955, October 28, 2005 - January 9, 2006] DATA: 2 of 2 Standard CDs SUMMARY: Participants give presentations and engage in discussions moderated by Robert Storr. RELATED MATERIAL: 2006.36 DONOR: Department of Education TRANSFERRED TO ARCHIVES: Fall 2006; NOTE: This recording is extremely difficult to hear (Item 2006.65b)
  - "Marcel Duchamp", 1964; PERSONALITY: Marcel Duchamp PARTICIPANTS: Marcel Duchamp, artist. SUMMARY: Marcel Duchamp discusses the concept of motion and the ideas that led to his painting Nude Descending a Staircase. DATA: 1 Standard CD. RELATED MATERIAL: 61.3, 61.4, 61.5, 61.6. TRANSFERRED TO ARCHIVES: May 2007. (Item 2007.1)
  - "Modern Danish Design Revisited", December 12, 2006; PLACE: The Museum of Modern Art SERIES: Think Modern: Adult and Academic Programs. PARTICIPANTS: Professor Penny Sparke, Dean of the Faculty of Art, Design & Music, Kingston University, London; Laetitia Wolff, writer, curator; Christina Strand, designer; Anders Byriel, director of the textile manufacturing company Kvadrat. SUMMARY: Panel discussion and lecture about the history and legacy of Danish design. DATA: 1 MP3 DONOR: Department of Education. TRANSFERRED TO ARCHIVES: May 2007. (Item 2007.2, 2007.2D)
  - "The Low Part of High Cubism", November 8, 1990; PERSONALITY: Robert Rosenblum PLACE: The Museum of Modern Art. SERIES: High and Low: Modern Art & Popular Culture PARTICIPANTS: Robert Rosenblum, professor and art historian. EXHIBITION:High and Low: Modern Art and Popular Culture[MoMA Exh. #1559, October 7, 1990-January 15, 1991] SUMMARY: Robert Rosenblum discusses the scholastic importance of cubism along with the realities outside the academic sphere. DATA: 1 Standard 90 Minute Audio Cassette. RELATED MATERIAL: 2001.28a, 2001.28b. DONOR: Department of Education TRANSFERRED TO ARCHIVES: May 2007. (Item 2007.3)
  - "World Art/Art World: Changing Perspectives on Modern and Contemporary Art", April 29, 2006; PLACE: The Museum of Modern Art SERIES: Graduate Symposia PARTICIPANTS: David Little, Director of Adult and Academic Programs, The Museum of Modern Art; Larissa Buchholz, Graduate student; Daniel Quiles, Graduate student; Jennifer Josten, Graduate Student; Roberta Bonetti, Graduate Student; Wendy Morris, Graduate student; Leora Maltz, Graduate Student; Zdenka Badovinac, Director of Moderna Galerija, Slovenia; Salah Hassan, Professor, Cornell University. SPONSOR: Education SUMMARY: Graduate lectures and discussion about the ramifications of globalism upon Art History, art markets and art careers. DATA: 1 MP3 DONOR: Department of Education. TRANSFERRED TO ARCHIVES: May 2007. (Item 2007.4)
  - "The Death of Film: A Millennial Symposium", January 11, 2000; PLACE: Titus Theater 2, The Museum of Modern Art PARTICIPANTS: Laurence Kardish, curator, Department of Film, The Museum of Modern Art; Godfrey Cheshire, film critic; John Bailey, cinematographer; Jason Kliot, co-founder of Open City Films; Rochelle Slovin, Director of the American Museum of the Moving Image; Dean Goodhill, film editor. SUMMARY: Laurence Kardish acts as moderator for a symposium concerned with the issues of digital cinema and how digital media will change the industry at large. DATA: 2 100 Minute Standard Audio Cassettes. DONOR: Department of Film. TRANSFERRED TO ARCHIVES: May 2007 (Item 2007.5a)
  - "The Death of Film: A Millennial Symposium", January 11, 2000; PLACE: Titus Theater 2, The Museum of Modern Art PARTICIPANTS: Laurence Kardish, curator, Department of Film, The Museum of Modern Art; Godfrey Cheshire, film critic; John Bailey, cinematographer; Jason Kliot, co-founder of Open City Films; Rochelle Slovin, Director of the American Museum of the Moving Image; Dean Goodhill, film editor. SUMMARY: Laurence Kardish acts as moderator for a symposium concerned with the issues of digital cinema and how digital media will change the industry at large. DATA: 2 100 Minute Standard Audio Cassettes. DONOR: Department of Film. TRANSFERRED TO ARCHIVES: May 2007 (Item 2007.5b)
  - "Robert Beers Memorial", December 9, 2005; PERSONALITY: Robert Beers, curator, Department of Film, The Museum of Modern Art. PLACE: The Museum of Modern Art. PARTICIPANTS: Laurence Kardish, curator, Department of Film, The Museum of Modern Art; Anne Javsicas; Charles S. Verral Jr.; Richard Hennessy; Lola Pashalinksi; Mary Vogler; Chris Rael; Penny Arcade, performance artist; Ken Tisa, professor; Robert Rindler, Dean of Cooper Union; Mickey Ronan, Community Organizer, Roosevelt Island; Jane White, actress; Jillian Slonim; Pat Whitman; Jennifer Smith, actress. SUMMARY: Participants share stories about Robert Beers. DATA: 1 90 Minute Standard Audio Cassette. DONOR: Department of Film TRANSFERRED TO ARCHIVES: May 20007. (Item 2007.6)
  - "Gabrielle", October 17, 2005; PERSONALITY: Isabelle Huppert PLACE: Titus Theater 1, The Museum of Modern Art SERIES: Film and Media Programs. PARTICIPANTS: Isabelle Huppert, actress; Patrice Chereau, director. SPONSOR: Cultural Services of the French Embassy. SUMMARY: Introductions by Patrice Chereau, director of the film and actress Isabelle Huppert. Followed by film screening. DATA: 1 60 Minute Standard Audio Cassette. DONOR: Department of Film. TRANSFERRED TO ARCHIVES: Spring 2007. (Item 2007.7)